HO WING LAW

MICKEY

About Me

As a Human Computer Interaction student with 3 year product design experience, I have always been keen to perceive the needs and wants of users and create solutions to solve genuine problems. I'm currently seeking interaction and experience design job opportunity.



Phone

+44 7561 762486



Email

lawhw.design@gmail.com



Linkedin

linkedin.com/in/mickeyhwlaw/



Portfolio

www.mickeylaw.design (•: hwlaw)

Skills

User Research
Design Ethnography
Information Visualisation
Solution Design
Prototyping
Usability Testing

Education

2019 - Present

MSC HUMAN COMPUTER INTERACTION

University of Nottingham

2012 - 2016

BA (HONOURS) IN PRODUCT DESIGN

Technological and Higher Education Institute of Hong Kong

- Graduated with First Class Honours
- GPA: 3.6/4.0

Experience

Oct 2016 -Aug 2019

PRODUCT DESIGNER II

VTech Telecommunications | Hong Kong

- Designed in-house telecommunication products for AT&T, Snom and VTech
- Conducted brand and customer research with a multinational team of 5 to redefine design directions and strategies
- Communicated and worked with project management team to follow up mass production

Nov 2013 -Mar 2014

RESEARCH PROJECT ASSISTANT - INTERNSHIP

Hong Kong Design Centre | Hong Kong

- Researched for influential designs and analysed relevant information into spreadsheets
- Evaluated potential designs in terms of their strong points, influence in Asia and commercial success

HO WING LAW

MICKEY

Awards

A' Design Award (Runner-up) 2019

Dean's List & President's List

Technological and Higher Education Institute of Hong Kong 2012 - 2016

Tools

Programming & Coding

Python CSS

HTML JavaScript

Softwares

Photoshop Sketch
Illustrator Principle
InDesign InVision

Adobe XD

Hobbies

Self-learning Japanese
(JLPT N3 qualified)
Meditating
Going to the gym
Visiting art museums
Reading
Watching documentaries

Volunteering / Leadership

Oct 2018 -Sep 2019

DESIGN SOCIETY VOLUNTEER

Design Society (co-founded with London's V&A)

Shenzhen, China

- Assisted the operations of events, such as design festivals, artists' and designers' talks
- Interacted with museum visitors and enhanced their visiting experience

2012 - 2013

EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE MEMBER - SECRETARY

Design Student's Society

THEi's Student Union, Hong Kong

- Collaborated with Engineering Student's Society to organise orientation camp
- Helped arrange sponsorship from organisations
- Recorded minutes at meetings

Certification

Mar 2018

DESIGN KIT:

THE COURSE FOR HUMAN-CENTERED DESIGN

IDEO

- Learned methods and tools of human-centered design
- Accomplished various design challenges
- Successfully came up with a healthy diet app concept with teammates and designed user flow and user interface